bitoffun.com 2016-03-12

# Privacy Policy

The privacy of our visitors to bitoffun.com is important to us. At bitoffun.com, we recognize that privacy of your personal information is important. Here is information on what types of personal information we receive and collect when you use and visit bitoffun.com, and how we safeguard your information. We never sell your personal information to third parties - ever.

## Log Files

As with most other websites, we collect and use the data contained in log files. The information in the log files include your IP (internet protocol) address, your ISP (internet service provider, such as Time Warner, Comcast or Shaw Cable), the browser you used to visit our site (such as Chrome, Internet Explorer or Firefox), the time you visited our site and which pages you visited throughout our site. 

## Cookies and Web Beacons 

We have two types of cookies. If you can smell the cookies don't grab them before they have had a chance to cool down. Be considerate and leave some for others. You may _not_ use them to entice people to join the dark side!

We also use cookies to store information, such as your personal preferences when you visit our site. This could include the ability to login to some of our features, such as forums. 

## Advertisements 

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here. ](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/)

You can chose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings, or by managing preferences in programs such as Norton Internet Security. However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites. This could include the inability to login to services or programs, such as logging into forums or accounts. 

## Advertiser Specific Details 

  * Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. 
  * Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. 
  * Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.  [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).
